西维吉尼亚州美湖镇 1814年建镇
1817年镇民集体消失无踪
至今原因不明
我爱你 比利
I love you,Billy.
天啊
Oh,my God.
该死 比利 我想你打断我的下巴了
Damn it,Billy. I think you broke my jaw.
你是活该 你们这些王八蛋!
You fucking deserve it, you assholes!
- 宝贝 你没事吧?  - 不
- Oh,are you okay,baby?  - No.
快给我滚开!
Get the fuck out of here!
你们干嘛打扮成那样?
What the hell are you doing dressed like that?
我们想打扮一下 庆祝山地人节
For the Mountain Man Festival, thought we'd dress up.
对 你们的服装在哪里?
Yeah,where are your costumes?
- 什么?  - 我们没有准备
- What?  - We don't have any.
没变装就不能去 那太不认真了
You can't go without a costume. It shows lack of commitment.
我们能等我穿好衣服后再谈吗?
Can we have this conversation after I can get dressed?
好吧
Okay. Okay.
很不错喔 比利...
Nice,Billy. Ha-ha-ha. Grrr...
太棒了 王八蛋
Nice. Assholes.
我是凯琳韦伯 在美湖镇为大家报导...
This is Kaleen Webber,reporting from the small town of Fairlake...
每年万圣节在这里会挤满了人...
which,once a year, turns into a big town on Halloween...
庆祝第十届山地人音乐节
due to the 10th annual Mountain Man Music Festival.
全国各地的年轻人来到美湖镇...
People from all over the country descend upon Fairlake...
整个周末享受音乐 派对 到镇外的游乐园玩个痛快
for a weekend of music,partying and fun at the fairgrounds just outside town.
音乐节规模越来越大 足以媲美对手...
The festival has grown over the years to where it now rivals...
柯契拉音乐节与洛拉帕洛查音乐节
Coachella and Lollapalooza.
有人说自由精神与喧闹群众 让他们想起火人祭...
But some say that its free spirit and rowdy crowds reminds them of Burning Man...
让当地警方非常担忧今晚的活动状况
which has local officials concerned on this night.
现在将镜头交还给棚内
Now back to you at the studio.
- 太棒了  - 听我说
- Great.  - Here's the deal.
我要去跑步 忘掉这个乱七八糟的小镇活动
I'm going for a run to get my head out of this town crap.
十一点我会回到这里做报导
I'll meet you here for the live feed at 11.
到时候最好一切准备都好了
And everything better be ready to go.
滚开 小鬼
Go away,kid. Ha-ha-ha.
快点 我们得上路了 我不想迟到
Hurry up. We gotta get on the road. I don't wanna be late.
好啊 给我一分钟时间清醒一下
All right, give me a minute to get up first.
我们听说你是一分钟男
We heard you're the one-minute man.
不 我可以保证绝对没有那回事
No. I assure you he has no problems in that department.
好吧 我饿坏了 我得先做早餐
All right. I'm starving. I gotta make breakfast first.
- 少来了 比利  - 早餐一定要吃
- Aw,come on,Billy.  - You gotta start your day out right.
哈哈
Ha,ha.
服装很不错 怪胎
Nice costume,creep.
你知道吗? 我厌倦了这一切
You know what? I'm sick of this.
我厌倦了你们这些孩子 只会跑趴 胡闹跟吓人
I'm sick of you kids partying, making a mess and trying to scare people.
你知道吗? 你吓不了我
Well,you know what? You don't scare me.
去你的 滚回家去吧
So fuck you. Go home.
救救我! 拜托! 快来人啊!
Help me! Help me,please! Somebody help me!
嘿 这边
Hey,hey. Over here.
请帮帮我 他们在追我
Oh,please help. They're chasing me.
跟我来 这边
Follow me. This way.
往下走
Down here.
好了
Okay.
好吧 我想他们离开了
Okay,I think they've gone.
谢谢 你从那些疯子手上救了我一命
Thank you. You saved me from those maniacs.
你流了很多血
Hey,you're bleeding pretty badly there.
我得帮你包紮一下
Let me fix that for you.
谢谢你
Thank God for you.
对 你该谢谢我
Yeah. Thank God for me.
用力压住伤口
Now,you keep pressure on that. Mm-hm.
- 待在这里别动  - 好的
- You stay here.  - Okay.
我去确定他们已经离开了
I'm gonna make sure they've gone.
- 好吧 没人了 往这边  - 好吧
- Okay,it's all clear. This way.  - Okay.
好吧
Okay,okay,okay.
可是...
But there's,uh...
- 我忘记告诉你一件事  - 什么?
- There's just one thing I forgot.  - What?
这个
This.
《致命弯道5：嗜血族》
嘿 帮个忙 好吗?
Hey,give me a hand,will you?
不 你这个大白癡
No,you fucking idiot.
我是指屍体
The body.
我的老天爷
Jesus fucking Christ.
- 这可以让你提提神 兄弟  - 谢了
- Wake and bake,brother.  - Thanks.
你这个邋遢鬼
Heh. You're such a slob.
就当是为了我 拜托你保持乾净一点?
Can you try and be a little bit cleaner for me?
- 什么?  - 你看起来跟猪差不多
- What?  - You look like a pig.
好吧 听我说
All right. Check it out.
我照日期跟时间 安排好所有的派对计划
I got all our party favors arranged by date and time.
这搞得我头都痛了
So this is cutting into my overhead.
不过为了欢庆这个周末 朱利安建议我们到这里的好点子...
But in honor of this weekend and Julian's great idea for us to come out here...
我特别破例
I've made an exception.
首先是你们的一些恶习
First up,some chronic, which you're participating in.
然后是限制级的不给糖就捣蛋...
And then some X for when we go trick or treating...
乐团一开始表演 我们就能茫翻天
and some shrooms for when the bands start playing. Oh.
比利 你已经休学两个学期
You've been out of school for two semesters.
- 你爸妈是怎么说的?  - 不 他们什么都不知道
- What do your parents think?  - Oh,no. They don't know shit.
我希望保持原状
And I wanna keep it that way.
而且我是新生代企业家
Ah,besides,you know, I'm a budding entrepreneur.
我们干嘛跑到这个鸟地方来?
Why did we have to come all the way out here?
因为我们要庆祝山地野人节
Because it's Mountain Man,baby.
别这样 听着 我们也可以参加火人祭
Hey,come on,look, we could have gone to Burning Man.
但我不想开车横跨美国
But I'm not gonna drive all the way across country.
在这里一样能玩得很开心
We got a homegrown version of it here.
而且山地人节的故事更有趣
Yeah. Mountain Man has got a much more interesting story to it,anyway.
- 克鲁丝 你知道这个故事吗?  - 我不是本地人 记得吗?
- You know the story,Cruz?  - I'm not from around here,remember?
好吧 我们要去美湖镇
Okay,well,we're going to a small town called Fairlake.
建镇年代大约是1814年
It was founded in 1814 or some shit like that.
显然当地矿工跟山区居民处不好
Well,apparently,the local miners didn't get along too well with the hill people.
我想他们是在争地盘
I guess it was a territory dispute.
接下来好几年冲突不断
There was conflicts over the next couple of years.
在1817年万圣节夜晚...
Now,Halloween night,1817...
山地人突袭全镇...
the entire town was ravaged by hillbillies...
酿成美国史上最严重集体屠杀事件
in the largest massacre in the state's history.
问题是找不到屍体
The only problem was no bodies were found.
只... 发现大量血迹 你懂的...
It was just... Just blood. Lots of it. It was... You know,it...
全镇的居民都不见了
The entire town, every inhabitant disappeared.
从此消失无踪
Was never seen again.
那真的很可怕...
That's awful. Well...
传说山地人把屍体拖进树林里...
Legend has it,the hillbillies hauled all the bodies up to the woods...
生火把美湖镇民的屍体煮熟
created a huge bonfire and then they cooked the fair residents of Fairlake.
然后吃进肚子里
Well... And then they ate them.
- 好吧 你们知道吗? 我不想去了  - 别这样 宝贝 我们就快到了
- Okay,you know what? I don't wanna go.  - Oh,come on,baby,we're almost there.
不 我不要庆祝大屠杀
No. I don't wanna celebrate a massacre.
- 这只是为了玩乐  - 那是不对的
- It's innocent fun.  - It's wrong.
我们今晚过去 明天就离开 好吗?别这样 克鲁丝
We'll just go tonight,we'll leave tomorrow,okay? Come on,Cruz.
一晚就好?
Just one night,huh?
拜托?
Please?
好吧
Okay,fine.
不会有事的
It is fine.
这是什么鬼东西?
What the fuck is all this shit?
我是怎么跟你说的?
What have I told you about this?
我跟你说过太多次...
I told you a thousand fucking times...
别留下任何证据
you never leave anything behind.
千万别留下任何证据!
You never ever leave anything behind!
如果被人发现了呢?
What if somebody found this,huh?
警察会开始调查 四处打探
Then you got oops investigating, snooping around.
你们不住在偏僻医院里了
You don't live in some goddamn hospital in the middle of nowhere any more.
这里离文明世界太近了
You live closer to civilization, a lot fucking closer!
我做这一行三十年了...
I have been doing this for 30 years...
从来不必搬家
and I have never had to move.
你们知道为什么?
Do you know why?
因为我从来不会留下证据!
Because I never leave shit behind!
我对天发誓 你们三个大笨蛋...
I swear to fucking God, you three pinheads...
要不是遇见我 你们早被关起来了
you'd all be under lock and key by now if I hadn't have happened across you.
你们住在我家 就得听我的
You live in my fucking house now and you play by my fucking rules.
乖乖照我的方式去做...
You do as I say...
不然我发誓我会杀了你们 管你们跟我是什么关系
or I swear to God, I will take you all down,kin or no kin.
把她处理好
Get her processed.
- 很期待这趟旅行吗?  - 对
- Looking forward to the trip?  - Yeah.
想像我拿着新步枪的帅模样
Thinking about getting me a new .30-60 for the occasion.
傑森真的很幸运 抽中猎熊执照乐透奖
It was lucky of Jason to win the bear license lottery.
我知道 他很兴奋
I know. He's very excited.
- 他真是个大好人 邀请我同行  - 我知道 所以我决定嫁给他
- Well,he's a good guy to invite me along.  - I know. That's why I married him.
- 你真的不想去?  - 我还有工作要做
- You sure you don't wanna come?  - I've got a job to do.
你得学着放轻松一点
You need to learn to relax a bit.
你总是一付严肃模样 像管理军队一样指挥着我们
You're always so by-the-book. You ride us like we're in the military.
纪律 朱尼尔 它是非常好用的生活工具
Discipline,Junior, it's a good tool to use in life.
你为今晚的活动准备好了吗?
Ready for tonight?
一群爱捣蛋的小鬼 超讨厌的
Mob of kids,such a pain in the keester.
今晚应该少不了 酒醉闹事跟滋扰治安的事件
It should be a big night for drunk and disorderly.
卡特警长
Sheriff Carter.
谁是绿荆郡最性感的警长?
Who is the sexiest sheriff in all of Greenbrier County?
我是绿荆郡唯一的警长
I'm the only sheriff in Greenbrier County.
那不代表你不性感
Still doesn't mean you're not sexy.
我刚值完第二班 现在要回家了
Hey,I just blew off the second shift. I'm headed home.
太棒了
That's good.
朱尼尔要买新步枪 这个周末跟你去打猎
Junior's buying a new rifle for your hunt this weekend.
跟他说那不代表他会比我厉害
Tell him it won't make him a better shot.
对 我已经跟他说过了
Yeah,I already did.
今天晚餐我要做千层面
I'm gonna fix some lasagna tonight for dinner.
- 要我带一些过去给你吗?  - 那就真的太棒了
- I'll stop by and bring you some?  - That would be great.
过来前先打电话联络一下 今晚应该会很忙
But call first. It's gonna be a busy night.
我可能会到游乐园去
I may head down to the fairgrounds.
那么我帮你把晚餐送到那里
Then I'll bring it to you there.
待会再联络 再见 老婆
I'll call you later. Bye,honey.
好的 再见 老公
Okay,bye,honey.
大声一点
Gotta turn this up.
应该会有二十支乐团到那里表演
There's supposed to be about 20 bands there.
- 谁要上台表演?  - 《花豹浪女》
- Oh,who's playing?  - The Cheetah Whores.
她们是谁?
Oh,who are they?
- 纯女子乐团 她们超棒的  - 对
- An all-girl band. Freaking awesome.  - Yeah.
- 葛斯最喜欢的乐团  - 噢
- Gus' favorite band.  - Oh.
如果她们真的那么厉害 为什么我没听说过她们?
If they're so awesome, why haven't I heard of them?
你来自西岸 她们不在那里表演
You're from the West Coast. They don't play there.
- 对了 你何时回去?  - 六月
- When are you gonna go back,by the way?  - Mm,June.
我只待一个月 陪陪我爸妈
But just for a month to see my parents.
- 比利要陪我一起去  - 对
- Billy is coming with me.  - Yeah.
- 太棒了  - 我们会玩得很开心
- Nice.  - We are gonna have an epic time.
跟爸妈见面? 那还蛮认真的
Meeting the folks? That's getting pretty serious.
谁? 我? 认真? 才怪
Who? Me? Serious? Never.
小心!
Look out!
大家没事吧?
Is everyone okay?
有人受伤吗?
Is anybody hurt?
- 我没事  - 不 我们都没事
- I'm all right.  - No,we're okay.
该死
Oh,shit.
他是从哪里冒出来的?
Where did he come from?
我们撞到他了吗?
Did We hit him?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
我们该去看看他是不是死了
Well,we should see if he's dead.
你们待在这里
You guys,stay here.
该死
Goddamn it.
下着雨 我根本没看到他
I didn't see him in the rain.
- 对 我想他死了  - 可是我没撞到他
- Yeah,I think he's dead.  - But I didn't hit him.
你一定有撞到他
You must have.
嘿
Hey.
去你的!
Fuck you! Unn!
你想耍我们吗?
You trying to fuck with us?
- 起来  - 你这个混蛋
- Get up.  - You piece of shit.
- 不要动  - 手放在头上
- Freeze.  - Put your hands on your head.
- 他拿刀砍我  - 手放在头上!
- He stabbed me.  - Put your hands on your head now!
不要动
Don't you move.
- 转身 朝我这边走过来  - 该死
- Turn around and walk towards me.  - Shit.
慢慢的
Slowly.
开始!
Go!
我要大家在车边等着 毕格斯
I want everyone to wait together by your vehicle. Biggs?
我会看着他们 警长
I've got them,sheriff.
不要动
Don't you move.
趴在地上
Face down on the ground.
右手放在背后
Right hand behind your back.
左手
Left hand.
转身
Turn around.
我需要厢型车支援 96号公路30英里处
I need a wagon. Route 96,mile marker 30.
- 收到 马上出发  - 太棒了 谢谢
- Copy that. On its way.  - Great,thanks.
警长
Hey,sheriff.
看起来那些孩子在开药局
It looks like we've got an entire pharmacy here.
音乐节都还没有开始呢
And the festival hasn't even started yet.
这会是漫长的一夜
It's gonna be a long night.
朱尼尔 你能留守在这里 等拖吊车过来吗?
Junior,can you stay with the car until the tow truck arrives?
我们得进行全面搜索 我不希望破坏证据
Until we get a search? I don't wanna mess up evidence.
没问题 警长
Sure thing,boss.
搞什么?
What the fuck?
嘿
Hey.
不要动
Hold it right there.
该死!
Shit!
(美湖镇警局)
嘿
Hey.
那应该可以了
That should do it.
三星期后再拆线
You need to have those stitches removed in about three weeks.
谢谢
Thank you.
我弄好了 警长
All done here,sheriff.
- 谢谢你赶过来 瑞克  - 别客气
- Thanks for coming,Rick.  - That's all right.
我知道今晚你会有多忙
I know how busy it's gonna get for you tonight.
- 再见  - 晚安
- Goodbye.  - Good night.
我不知道该怎么办
You know,I just don't know what I'm gonna do.
我被起诉的话 奖学金就会被取消
If I get charged,they're gonna take my scholarship away from me.
- 我们会被退学的  - 比利 你得告诉她
- We can get kicked out of school.  - Billy,you gotta tell her.
- 那是你的毒品 与我们无关  - 不 如果他说那都是他的
- It was your drugs,not ours.  - No,no. If he claims it's all his...
- 他们会逮捕他  - 我不在乎
- they could throw the book at him.  - I don't care.
他害我被关在拘留所里
I'm sitting in jail because of him.
- 我不知道该怎么办  - 好了 别担心 好吗?
- I just don't know what I'm gonna do.  - All right,hey,don't worry,all right?
我会处理的
I got this.
警长 我们能谈一谈吗?
Sheriff,can I speak with you a moment?
有什么事吗?
What is it?
毒品是我的 跟我的朋友们无关
The drugs are mine. My friends had nothing to do with it.
那一点还有待确认
That's to be determined.
它们真的是我的 他们可以作证
Honestly,they're mine. They'll tell you.
他说的没错
He's right.
拜托你放了他们 我会负起责任
Please let them go. I'll take responsibility.
好吧 反正我得为今晚预留牢房
All right. I'm gonna need space tonight, anyway.
别离镇
Don't leave town.
我们哪里都不会去
We won't go anywhere.
街的尽头有家汽车旅馆
There's a motel at the end of the street.
- 谢谢  - 去领你们的东西
- Thanks.  - Come get your things.
我们会带晚餐来给你 比利
We'll bring you back some dinner,Billy.
谢谢
Thanks.
嘿 那我呢?
Hey,what about me?
你看到他们攻击我 为什么我要被关起来?
You saw how they attacked me. Why am I being held?
持致命武器伤人
Assault with a deadly weapon.
- 那是胡说八道  - 那孩子手臂的伤口证明了一切
- That's bullshit.  - The out on the boy's arm says otherwise.
至少你能帮我换间牢房吧?
Well,would you at least move me to another cell?
这个酒鬼臭死了
This drunk stinks.
你能撑过来的
You'll survive.
- 她在哪里?  - 我打了一小时手机找她
- Where is she?  - I've been calling her cell for the last hour.
- 她没接  - 该死的爱现鬼
- She's not picking up.  - Freaking diva.
我讨厌选秀会
I hate talent.
你得帮她代打
You're gonna have to fill in.
什么?
What?
不 我没办法
No,I can't.
你可以的 你非这么做不可
You can and you will.
我绝对不准节目开天窗
No one goes to dead air on my watch.
好吧
Okay.
我们在西维吉尼亚州美湖镇大街
Here we are on Main Street in the town of Fairlake,West Virginia.
孩子们跑到街上疯狂庆祝万圣节...
The kids are out for Halloween in full force...
不过有一群山地人加入他们...
but they're joined by a bunch of hillbillies...
一起庆祝第十届山地人音乐节
for the 10th annual Mountain Man Music Festival.
不论你打扮成鬼 女巫或山地人...
So whether you're dressed as a ghost or a witch or a hillbilly...
大家都能欢度万圣节...
everyone is sure to have a happy Halloween...
享受一流音乐表演
with some great music to top it all off.
这就是目前的状况
That's all for now.
我是薇吉妮雅凯利 现场直播新闻台报导
I'm Virginia Kelly from Live Action News.
做得好
Good job.
(葛洛佛汽车旅馆 电暖器 有线电视 尚有空房)
- 是这间吗?  - 应该是
- Is this it?  - Oh,3,this is it.
看起来还可以
It looks all right.
- 太棒了  - 这是我们的床 葛斯
- Nice.  - This is our bed,Gus.
(小马纳德奥迪特)
看起来你逃亡了一阵子
Seems like you've been running for quite some time.
你的亡命生涯结束了
Well,your running just ended.
杀人罪没有追溯期限
There is no statute of limitations for murder.
你不知道自己惹到谁了 对吧?
You have no idea what you've gotten yourself into,do you?
我想我得填写一大堆文件
A lot of paperwork,I suspect.
美国执法官办公室
U. S. Marshal's office.
我是美湖镇的卡特警长
Yeah,this is Sheriff Carter in Fairlake.
我抓到一名逃犯
I have a fugitive for you.
他逃亡三十年
He's been on the run for 30 years.
- 他叫什么名字?  - 马纳德奥迪特
- What's his name?  - Maynard Odets.
案号是316165
Case number 316165.
我们明天早上十点过去接他
We can have transport there by 10 a.m.
好的 没问题
Yeah,that'll be fine.
明天一大早 执法官会来接你
The marshals will be here to pick you up in the morning.
你活不了那么久
You won't live that long.
我才不相信你的鬼话
I highly doubt that.
不 我知道
No,I... No,I know. I know.
不 对 但那是个意外
No,it's... Yeah,but it was a complete accident.
那是... 对
It was an a... Yeah.
明天
Tomorrow.
车子全毁
The car is totaled.
不 我派其他警官到游乐园 维持音乐节的秩序
No,I sent the other deputies to the fairgrounds to police the festival.
朱尼尔除外
All except Junior.
这倒提醒了我 他早该回来了
Which reminds me, he should be back by now.
傑森?
Jason?
布洛汀先生?
Mr. Brodin?
布洛汀先生... 手机断讯 这样也好
Mr. Brodin... Lost the signal. Probably for the best.
说比利的爸爸气坏了 还算是轻描淡写
To say Billy's dad is pissed is the understatement of the year.
- 明天他会过来?  - 对
- Is he coming tomorrow?  - Yeah.
你觉得比利的麻烦有多大?
How much trouble do you think Billy's in?
天啊 那一包毒品不少
Oh,God,there's a lot of drugs in that bag.
我想他的罪名不只是行为不检
I don't think he's gonna get off with a misdemeanor.
你觉得比利会因此去坐牢吗?
Do you think Billy's gonna go to jail?
比利的爸爸会帮他找最好的律师 因为他超有钱的
Billy's dad will throw the best lawyers because Billy's dad is loaded.
- 或许不需要 他可能会走运  - 对 我一点都不担心
- He might not have to. He might get lucky.  - Yeah. I wouldn't worry about it.
比利的爸爸关系超好的
Billy's dad's connected up to the Wazoo.
好吧 我们去参加音乐节
Okay,so let's go to the festival.
你在说什么? 朱利安 现在我们不能去参加音乐节
What the hell,Julian? We can't go now.
待在旅馆房间也帮不了比利 有何不可呢? 我们...
Well,we can't help Billy sitting in a hotel room. Why not? We...
来吧 我们大老远跑到这里来
Come on,we came all this way.
- 你提议我们怎么去参加音乐节?  - 走路过去
- And how do you propose we get there?  - Uh,walk.
我哪里都不去 各位 拿去吧 宝贝
Well,I'm not going anywhere,guys. Here,babe.
该死的小酒鬼
Damn drunk kids.
嘿!
Hey!
这是怎么一回事?
What the hell's going on here?
麻烦你闭嘴?
Will you shut up?
开始了
It's started.
他们来救我 你死定了
They're coming for me and you're dead.
只是你还不知道
But you don't know it yet.
谁要来救你?
Who's coming for you?
我的孩子们
MY boys.
他们会挖出你的肝脏 在你面前吃掉它
They're gonna cut your liver out and eat it in front of you.
我不想跟这傢伙关在一起 拜托帮我换间牢房
I don't wanna be in here with this guy. Can you please put me in the other cell?
你们都死定了
You're all dead.
小子 你听到了吗?
You hear me,kid?
去你的 老头
Fuck you,old man.
你可以回家了 莫斯
You can go home,Mose.
- 其他警察在哪里?  - 他们去维持音乐节秩序
- Where are your deputies?  - Covering the festival.
- 或许我该留下来?  - 为什么?
- Maybe I should stick around?  - What for?
没有人陪你 以防万一
You got nobody with you,just in case.
没事的 莫斯 他只是个疯老头
It's fine,Mose. He's just a crazy old man.
以防万一
Just in case.
如果你不介意 就那么决定了
If you don't mind,that is.
好吧 麻烦你帮帮忙
Okay,but make yourself useful.
找一下抽屉里有没有手电筒
Go through the drawers for the flashlights.
灯光救不了你
Light ain't gonna save you.
如果你不闭嘴 我要以威胁警察罪名起诉你
If you don't shut up,I'm gonna charge you with threatening an officer.
尽管起诉我吧 警长
Hey,charge away,officer.
该死
Shit.
天啊
Oh,my God.
- 他在这吗?  - 天啊 不在
- Here.  - Oh,my God.
警官好
Hi,officer.
我想我走错路了
I think I took a wrong turn.
你能告诉我后台怎么去吗?
Can you tell me how to get backstage?
又走错路了?
Another wrong turn,huh?
我可以带你过去 但你需要通行证才能进去
I can show you, but you need a pass to get in.
为了拿到通行证 我什么都愿意做
I will do anything to get a pass.
说到底就是你得死翘翘了
Oh,there's no use talking to you Dead end,true
这就是我所想的 到时她会提醒你的
This is what I'm thinking Oh,she'll remind you
到你看到只需要一秒
Only take a second Till you see I'm just a fake
该死
Shit.
毕格斯警官 请回答
Deputy Biggs,come in.
朱尼尔 我是安琪拉 请回答
Junior,it's Angela,come in.
麦克 凯文 你们听到了吗?
Mike,Kevin,you guys out there?
这就是我所想 她到时会提醒你
This is what I'm thinking Oh,she'll remind you
听起来只剩你一个人了 你这个白癡贱人
Looks like you're all alone, you dumb bitch.
四张90块门票 一共是260块
Four tickets at 90 bucks a pop, that's 260 bucks.
太棒了
Mm,great.
我们只能呆坐在黑夜中
So we sit around in the dark all night.
这真的太好玩了
So much fun. So much fun.
太棒了
It's great.
你们知道吗? 我要送食物给比利吃
You know what? I'm gonna go and take Billy some food.
你觉得拘留所也停电了吗?
You think all the power's out in the jail as well?
看起来全镇都停电了
Oh,looks like the whole town's out.
对 不 当然全镇都停电了
Yeah. No,of course not. The whole town's out. The whole town's out.
他们在演唱会上玩得很开心 我们也该那么做
At the concert,having a good time like we should be.
拿去吧 带着手电筒
Here,take this with you.
谢谢
Oh,thanks.
- 待会见  - 再见 宝贝
- See you later.  - See you,babe.
- 再见  - 再见
- See you.  - Bye.
哈啰?
Hello?
两位
Um,guys?
Guys.
两位
- 什么?  - 我要去找比利
- Yeah?  - I'm gonna go see Billy.
- 酷啊  - 我给你们一些隐私
- Cool.  - I'm giving you guys some privacy.
啊!
Aah! Unn!
万圣节快乐 混蛋
Happy Halloween,asshole.
大混蛋!
Son of a bitch!
啊...
Ahh...
拿去吧
There you go.
你来这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
我想来陪比利跟克鲁丝
I thought I'd hang out with Billy and Cruz.
克鲁丝不在这里
Cruz isn't here.
什么?那太奇怪了 二十分钟前她带食物来找你
What? That's weird. She left with food about 20 minutes ago.
她在哪里?
Well,where is she?
我以为她到这里来了 或许她改变了心意 回旅馆了
I thought she came here. Maybe she changed her mind.
访客时间结束 明天早上再来吧
Visiting hours are over. Come in the morning.
别这样 我不能在这里待一下吗?
Oh,come on. Can't I just hang out here for a little while?
对 你何不让他留下来?
Yeah,why don't you let him stay?
这下子可以多一具屍体
One more dead body to add to the pile.
搞什么?
What the fuck?
这个老混蛋一直嚷嚷着要杀了大家
This old bastard has been promising to kill everybody.
他说他的孩子们会来救他
He says his boys are coming to break him out.
这里只有你跟那个酒鬼
And it's just you and the drunk.
- 说话小心点 孩子 我酒醒了  - 你最好先离开
- Watch your mouth,kid. I'm sober now.  - It's probably best if you go.
你不需要帮手吗? 以防这傢伙是说真的
Wouldn't you want another hand in case this guy's telling the truth?
你可以待在这里等你朋友 然后你们一起回汽车旅馆
You can stay until your friend gets here. Then you can walk back to the hotel.
- 你是怎么了?  - 有些死小孩拿漆弹打我
- What happened to you?  - Fucking kids hit me with a paint balloon.
所以你该跟那女孩回汽车旅馆去
That's why you should walk back with the girl.
好吧
All right.
兄弟
Hey,man.
你跟我爸谈过了?
So you talked to my dad?
对 我知道 他超级火大的
Yeah,I know,he's really,really,really extremely,monumentally pissed.
我想像得到
Well,I guess I expected that.
对 明天一早他会来帮你办交保
Yeah,he'll be here in the morning to post bail.
她有说要用什么罪名起诉你吗?
Did she say what she's charging you with?
她没说 但那些毒品足以让我的罪名成立
She didn't say, but there was enough stuff for a felony.
天啊 我搞砸了 对吧?
Man,I'm fucked,aren't I?
对 他超变态的
Yeah,he's creepy as fuck.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
丽塔...
Lita...
- 什么?  - 我一直在想
- What? - I've been thinking.
好吧
Okay.
五月时我们就要毕业
We both graduate in May.
我想我们可以住在一起
And I was thinking we could move in together.
葛斯 别这样 你知道我要搬到纽约
Gus,come on, you know I'm moving to New York.
我已经找到工作了
I've got my job lined up.
当会计超无聊的
But accounting is so boring.
别去
Don't go.
宝贝 我们谈过很多次了
Babe,we've talked about this a thousand times.
我非去不可
I'm going.
那么我跟你一起去
Then I'll go with you.
听着...
Look...
葛斯 我喜欢你
Gus,I like you.
我甚至爱你
I might even love you.
可是...
But...
我不知道 我只是...
I don't know,I just...
我需要独处一下
I need to spend some time on my own.
你懂吗?
You understand that?
丽塔 我爱你
Lita,I love you.
我不想失去你
And I don't wanna lose you.
嫁给我吧
Marry me.
什么?
What?
天啊
Oh,my God.
你在西维吉尼亚州的三流汽车旅馆...
You're proposing to me in some flea bag motel...
葛斯 跟我求婚? 少来了
in the middle of West Virginia? Gus,come on.
- 心意最重要  - 对
- It's the thought that counts.  - Yeah.
宝贝...
Babe...
别这样
come on.
在朱利安回来前把衣服穿好 我得沖个澡
Get dressed before Julian comes back. I'm gonna take a shower.
对不起
I'm sorry.
好吧 我听到了 别猴急
All right. I heard you. Keep your shirt on.
你是谁?
Who the fuck are you?
你找错房间了 快滚开
You got the wrong hotel room,pal. Move along.
你醉到连话都说不出来吗?
Are you so fucking drunk you don't speak English?
我要你滚开 笨蛋
I said,move along,you dumb shit.
葛斯 是谁?
Gus,who was that?
音乐节的酒鬼
Some drunk guy from the festival.
他找错房间了
Couldn't find his room.
噢
Oh.
但他的服装蛮酷的
Cool costume though.
该死 笨蛋淋浴
Ow. Fuck. Stupid thing.
我没办法沖澡
Stupid shower doesn't work.
是冷水
It's freezing.
该死 王八蛋
Goddamn,you son of a bitch.
听着 我跟你的酒鬼朋友说过 你们找错房间了
Look,I already told your drunk little buddy you got the wrong room.
你们到底有什么毛病?
What is it with you people?
什么 你们是智障吗?
What,are you fucking retarded?
葛斯?
Gus?
葛斯 怎么了?
Gus,what was that?
克鲁丝到底在哪里? 她不可能到现在还没到
So where the hell is Cruz? It can't have taken her this long to get here.
- 我不知道 你要我去找她吗?  - 或许她已经死了
- I don't know. You want me to look for her?  - She's probably dead.
我的孩子们已经在街上把她抓走
My boys already got to her on the street.
闭上你的鸟嘴 老头
Shut the fuck up,old man.
你爱怎么说都可以 大学生...
You can say what you like,college boy...
但你的死期到了
but your reckoning is on its way.
你能叫那个死老头闭嘴吗?
Hey,can you just shut this old bastard up?
我真的没办法再听他胡扯下去了
I can't stand listening to him any more.
我不能封住他的嘴巴 如果你是那个意思
Well,I can't gag him if that's what you're saying.
给我五分钟时间跟他独处 他会安静一整个晚上
Give me five minutes with him and he'll be quiet for the night.
你惹的麻烦够多了 年轻人 别理他
You've got yourself in enough trouble, young man. Just ignore him.
葛斯?
Gus?
不
No.
拜托
Please.
不
No.
应该是她来了
That's probably her now.
甜心 怎么了?
Hey,sweetheart. How's it going?
今晚还蛮有趣的
It's been an interesting night.
对 我发现停电 於是帮你带了些蜡烛过来
Yeah. I saw the power outage and I thought I'd bring you some candles.
- 你还好吧?  - 我很好 谢谢你 老公
- Are you okay?  - Yeah,I'm fine. Thanks,honey.
- 莫斯 你能帮我点蜡烛吗?  - 没问题
- Mose,can you light some of these for me?  - Sure.
发生了什么事?
So,what's going on?
我抓到一个逃犯 执法官会来接他...
I've got a fugitive who's being picked up by the marshals...
...还有犯了毒品罪的小鬼
...and a kid on drug charges.
- 我相信好戏才刚刚上场  - 对 或许是吧
- And I bet your night is just starting.  - Heh. Yeah,probably is.
- 你饿了吗?  - 我饿坏了
- You hungry?  - Starving.
为什么你不叫你的手下 回来吃三明治?
Why don't call your deputies and come home for a sandwich?
我无法联络上他们 而且我该待在这里
I can't reach them and besides,I should really stay here.
他们哪里都去不了 你得休息一下 你知道吗?
Those guys aren't going anywhere. Take some time for yourself,you know?
警长也有午休时间
Even the sheriff is entitled to a lunch break.
- 傑森  - 好吧
- Jason.  - All right.
我去做些三明治 待会帮你送过来
I'll go fix some sandwiches and I'll be back in a bit.
最后晚餐
Last supper.
他有什么问题?
What's his problem?
- 那傢伙是谁?  - 别说了
- Who is that guy?  - Don't ask.
好吧 待会见
Okay. See you soon.
待会见
See you later.
救命啊!
Help!
快来救救我!
Somebody help!
拜托! 救命啊!
Please! Help!
救救我!
Help me!
停车! 拜托 停车!
Stop! Please stop!
快来救救我!
Somebody help!
快来人啊!
Somebody!
救命啊!
Help!
救救我!
Help me!
放了我 你这个该死的疯子
Let me go,you crazy fuck.
你们要做什么?
What are you doing?
不
No.
No. No.
求求你们 不要
Please,no,no.
五毛钱
Fifty cents.
一块...
Buck. Uh...
跟了
Call.
他们是谁?
Who are they?
我不知道 我没看过那辆卡车
I don't know. I never seen the truck before.
我早跟你说过
I told you.
是我的孩子们 他们来救我了
It's my boys. They're here to get me.
该死
Shit.
- 救命啊!  - 是葛斯
- Help!  - That's Gus.
快来人啊 拜托!
Somebody,please!
救命啊!
Help!
天啊 我们得把他从路上搬开
Oh,God. We gotta get him out of the middle of the road.
我没办法
Oh,I can't. I can't.
快来帮帮我
Give me a hand.
警长 死了一个人吗?
One down,huh,sheriff?
你哪里都去不了 你得为此付出代价
You're not going anywhere and you're gonna pay for this.
混蛋 你听到了吗?
You hear me,you bastard?
我们该怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
出来
Get out.
- 我得去找克鲁丝  - 还有丽塔
- I need to find Cruz.  - And Lita.
听我说
Listen to me.
现在你们都是警察
You're all deputized.
如果你们愿意帮我 我会在法庭上帮你美言几句
If you help me,it will go a long way in my report to the court.
- 我得去找我的女朋友  - 不 我们都得待在这里
- But I wanna go after my girlfriend.  - No,we all stay here.
我们得等救援赶来
We hold out until help arrives.
莫斯 你负责前门
Mose,you watch the front door.
你们两个负责窗户
You two,cover the windows.
他们要分散我们 那样子他们比较容易下手
They want us to split up. It makes it easier for them to kill us that way.
我们得待在一起 等待天亮 好了 各就各位
So we should stick together, here until dawn. Now,get to your stations.
- 我们得打电话求援  - 室内电话不通 手机也一样
- We need to call for help.  - Lines are dead. Cell too.
警长 李的二手商店后面 有个短波无线电 我看过
Uh,sheriff,uh,Lee has a short-wave radio in the back of his thrift store. I've seen it.
- 我们需要电力才能使用无线电  - 李有发电机 好点子
- We need power to operate it.  - Lee has a generator. Good thinking.
听着 我要过街到他的店里
Listen,I'm gonna go across the street to the store.
我会利用短波无线电求救
I'm gonna fire up the shortwave and call for help.
- 我陪你去  - 不
- I'll go with you.  - No,no,no.
你待在这里 别让他们进来
You stay and make sure they don't get in.
那不是个好点子 警长
Not a bright idea there,sheriff.
- 分开来就会死掉 记得吗?  - 他说得对
- Split up and die,remember?  - He's right.
我不会拿你们的生命安全冒险
I will not risk your lives.
这是我的工作 我在街上时帮我掩护
This is my job. Now,cover me when I'm on the street.
(二手商店)
好吧
Okay.
好吧 你在哪里?
Okay,where are you?
好吧 快点
Okay,come on.
你在哪里?
Where are you? Where are you? Where are you?
太棒了
Yes.
(欢迎光临李叔二手商店)
好吧
Okay.
汽油
Gas.
有了
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
- 我们该去帮她  - 不 我答应过我会待在这里
- We should go help her.  - Nope. I gave my word I'd stay here.
- 我去帮她  - 等一下
- I'll go.  - Give it a minute.
- 如果再听到枪声 我们就去帮她  - 但我们没有...
- Just... If we hear another shot,we'll go.  - But we don't...
我们不认识这个女人 她不是克鲁丝或丽塔
We don't know this woman. She's not Cruz or Lita.
- 我们该去找她们 等一下  - 那我们就去找女孩们
- We should be going after them. Just wait.  - Let's go find the girls.
你一离开 他们会起诉你 等一下 看看她会不会回来
If you leave,they'll throw the book at you. Wait a few minutes,see if she comes.
- 她回来后 再跟她说我们要离开  - 好吧
- If she does,we'll tell her we're both going.  - All right.
十分钟
Ten minutes.
我是美湖镇卡特警长 通报紧急事件
This is Sheriff Carter of Fairlake declaring emergency.
有人听到吗? 完毕
Is anyone out there? Over.
西维吉尼亚州美湖镇卡特警长 通报紧急事件
Sheriff Carter of Fair/ake,West Virginia declaring an emergency.
有人听到吗? 完毕
Can anyone hear me? Over.
我听到了 警长
Yup,I hear you,sheriff.
你叫什么名字? 你在哪里?
What's your name and where are you?
泰迪塔伯特 我在新罕布夏州迪克斯维尔山口
Uh,Teddy Tabet. I'm in Dixville Notch,New Hampshire.
好吧 仔细听我说 泰迪
Okay,listen to me carefully,Teddy.
我要你打电话给 在芒兹维尔的维吉尼亚州警
I need you to call the Virginia State Police in Moundsville.
请他们立刻调派所有人力到美湖镇
Have them send every available officer to Fairlake right away.
这是紧急状况
It's an emergency.
发生了什么事?
What's going on down there?
三个山地人围攻本镇 他们想要闯入警局...
The town is under siege by three hillbillies. They're trying to break...
营救被关在拘留所的亲人 他们已经杀了一个人
one of their relatives out of jail. They've already killed one person already.
你说西维吉尼亚州美湖镇吗?
Did you say Fairlake,West Virginia?
没错 我们的电话不通
Yes,that's right. And we have no phone service.
我要你立刻打电话给州警 你能那么做吗?
So I need you to call the state police right away. Can you do that?
好吧 等一下
Okay,okay. One minute.
你嗑了药吗?
Are you stoned?
什么?
What?
你是嗑了药或在耍我?
Are you stoned or do you just think I'm stupid?
你在胡说什么?泰迪 我需要你帮忙
What are you talking about,Teddy? I need your help.
今晚是山地人节吗?
Tonight's the Mountain Man Festival, right?
你觉得那很好玩 你能整翻州警...
You think it would be funny to scramble the entire state police...
因为你能说服某个呆瓜 帮你打电话?
because you convinced some dork to call?
这是真的
This is real.
我是警长 我需要你帮忙
I am the sheriff and I need your help.
事态严重 泰迪
This is serious,Teddy.
听着 乱打电话报警是犯法的
Hey,listen,it's a felony to file a fake police report,okay?
我不是笨蛋 迪克斯维尔山口的人水准很高
I'm not stupid. We here in Dixville Notch are a pretty savvy bunch.
你是骗不了我的
You can't pull the wool over my eyes.
好吧 晚安 警官
So,uh,yeah,heh, have a good night,officer.
等一下 拜托 听我说 泰迪 你得相信我
Wait,wait,wait. Please,listen,Teddy, you gotta believe me.
这件事攸关生死
This is a matter of life and death.
- 该死  - 那是什么声音?
- Shit.  - What was that?
有人快死了
Somebody dying.
现在你相信我了吗?混蛋 快报警
You believe me now,asshole? Just call the police.
- 我想我打中一个了  - 该死
- I think I got one of them.  - Shit,shit.
大白癡 如果是警长呢?
You idiot. What if that was the sheriff?
你受伤了吗?
Are you hurt?
天啊 那是葛斯吗?
Oh,my God. Is that Gus?
那是葛斯吗?
Is that Gus?
快进去
Come inside.
天啊
Oh,my God.
好吧 你没事了
All right,okay. You're all right. You're all right.
朱利安 让我进去
Julian,let me in.
- 发生了什么事?  - 这个酒鬼差点杀死我朋友
- What happened?  - This drunk nearly killed my friend.
我真的很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- 他不该拿枪的  - 那是个意外!
- He has no business carrying a gun.  - It was an accident!
- 我该痛扁你一顿  - 冷静
- I should beat this shit out of you! Hey,calm down.  - Calm down.
我要你冷静点
I said,calm down.
- 你有受伤吗?  - 没有
- Were you hit?  - No.
好吧 你看到克鲁丝了吗?
Okay. Have you seen Cruz?
你跟她在一起吗?
Were you with her?
她比我先出门 朱利安
She left before Julian.
她死了 白马王子
She's dead,lover boy.
或许她被吞进胜子了
Probably being digested right now.
我的孩子们喜欢吃人肉...
My boys have a taste for flesh...
特别是金发小美女
especially cute little blonds.
给我闭嘴?
Will you shut the fuck up?
如果她真的出事 我会杀了你
If anything happened to her, I'm gonna fucking kill you.
放了我...
Let me go...
或许其他人能活着看到天亮
and maybe the rest of them will live to see the dawn.
你不能离开
You're not getting out of there.
你们只有四个人 再加上她
There's four of you and one of her.
想一下你们到底要不要活命
Think how much you wanna live.
如果你觉得我们会放了你 你一定是疯了
You're out of your mind if you think any one of us is gonna let you out.
随便你
Suit yourselves.
你用短波无线电 联络上任何人了吗?
Did you reach anybody on the short wave?
- 有  - 太棒了 那代表救援很快会赶到
- Yes.  - Great. That means help is coming.
- 我不知道  - 你是什么意思?
- I don't know.  - What do you mean?
我想收到讯息的笨蛋不相信我
The dumb shit on the other line, I don't think he believed me.
- 我要去找克鲁丝  - 我说过不行
- I'm going to look for Cruz.  - Hey,I told you,no.
- 那么你得把我关起来  - 什么?
- Well,then you better lock me back up.  - What?
好吧 或许我搞砸了
All right,I may be a fuck up.
我不负责任 不可靠 非常幼稚 但我非常忠诚
I'm irresponsible,I'm unreliable and I'm definitely juvenile,but I am loyal.
我爱克鲁丝
I love Cruz.
她是我一生的最爱...
I love her more than anything I've ever loved in my life...
...我不会待在这里 放她一个人在外面
...and I'm not gonna sit in here while she's out there on her own.
我无法允许自己那么做
I couldn't live with myself if I did that.
你要不把我关起来 要不就放了我
So either lock me up or let me go.
- 拿去吧 你会需要这个  - 谢谢
- Here,you're gonna need this.  - Thank you.
- 我跟你一起去  - 好吧
- I'm going with you.  - All right.
你没事吧?
You gonna be all right?
小心点
Be careful.
我们会的
We Will.
我们得四处看一下 试着寻找她
We'll look around here, see if we can find her.
好吧 眼睛睁大一点
All right. Keep your eyes open.
克鲁丝
Cruz.
克鲁丝 我是比利
Cruz,it's Billy.
快出来
Come out.
如果克鲁丝发现不对劲 她会躲起来 不肯出来
If Cruz knows what's up, she'll be hiding and won't come out.
对
Yeah.
希望真的是那样
I hope that's the case.
- 先生?  - 叫我莫斯就好了
- Mister?  - Call me Mose.
为什么他们要这么做?
Why are they doing this?
我想他们是来救他的
They wanna break him out,I suppose.
但他们屠杀无辜的人?
But killing innocent people?
为什么要杀死葛斯?
Why kill Gus?
那个老头被关起来的事跟他无关
He had nothing to do with keeping that old guy locked up.
我想杀人对这些傢伙来说 是稀松平常的事
I get the feeling that killing ain't too much of a stretch for this bunch.
如果没有人来救我们呢?
What if no help comes?
一定会有人来救我们 别担心
It will. Don't worry.
比利跟朱利安呢?
And Billy and Julian?
他们会找到你的朋友...
They'll find your friend...
一起回到这里
and then they'll be back.
克鲁丝!
Cruz!
你听到了吗?
Are you out there?
- 她到底会在哪里?  - 我不知道
- Where the hell could she be?  - I don't know,man.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
那是什么声音?
What the hell was that?
快点 比利
Move,Billy.
该死
Shit. Shit.
我们得离开街道 在这里我们只能坐以待毙
We gotta get out of the street. We're sitting ducks.
那边
There.
该死 克鲁丝
Oh,shit. Cruz.
天啊 宝贝
Oh,my God,baby.
天啊
Oh,my God.
Oh,
克鲁丝
Cruz.
他们是哪门子的禽兽?
What kind of fucking animals are they?
现在我们救不了她
There's nothing we can do for her now.
我要带她回去
I'm taking her back.
我不要让她跟垃圾一样横屍街头
I'm not gonna leave her here like some piece of trash.
天啊
Oh,Jesus.
大混蛋
Son of a bitch.
比利!
Billy!
朱利安
Julian.
朱利安!
Julian!
醒一醒!
Wake up!
- 天杀的  - 该死
- Fuck.  - Shit.
天啊 比...
Oh,God,Bi...
- 比利 发生了什么事?  - 我动不了
- Billy,what's going on?  - I can't move.
我动不了 你得把链子解开
I can't move. You gotta get out of that chain,man.
链子?
Chain?
解得开吗?
Can you get out?
该死
Shit.
该死... 不行
Fuck. No. Just... No.
- 该死  - 不...
- Fuck.  - No,there's...
我们得呼救 好吗?
We gotta call for help. All right?
救命啊!
Help!
- 救救我们 快来人啊!  - 救命啊!
- Help us,anybody!  - Help!
- 快来人啊!  - 救命啊!
- Anybody!  - Help!
该死
Fuck.
他在哪里?
Where is he? Where is he?
Where is he?
天啊
Oh,my,God. Oh,my,God.
救命啊!
Help!
救救我们!
Help us!
快来人啊!
Anybody!
救命啊!
Help!
朱利安 救救我
Julian. Julian,save me.
救救我... 快帮我!
Save... Help me,man!
搞什么... 搞毛线呀?
What the... What the fuck?
不 不要
No,don't. No,don't.
该死
Fuck.
不 不要... 丢下我
No,don't... Don't leave me.
朱利安 不要丢下我
Julian,don't leave me. Don't leave me.
不!
No!
不! 不!
No! No! No!
朱利安! 停下来 你这个混蛋!
Julian! Stop it,you motherfucker!
什么?
What?
(主队 客队)
我们不能整晚待在这里 等他们回来
We can't sit here all night and wait for them to come back.
- 我们得派人去求救  - 对 那个人就是你 莫斯
- Somebody needs to go for help.  - Yes,and that has to be you,Mose.
你办得到吗?
Can you do it?
嘿 丽塔
Hey,Lita.
你何不救救自己呢?
Why don't you save yourself?
我该怎么做?
How?
说服她放了我
Convince her to let me out of here.
- 我可以的  - 开我的车
- I can do it,sheriff.  - Take my truck.
到游乐园找朱尼尔...
Take it to the fairgrounds and find Junior...
还有其他警察 要他们回警局
and the other deputies and bring them back here.
不论如何 千万别停车
Do not stop for anyone or anything.
我跟我的孩子们...
Me and my boys will go...
会消失在夜色里 你会很安全的
disappear into the night. You'll be safe.
我不相信你
I don't trust you.
为什么我要被困在这里?
Why would I stick around here?
好好想一下
Think about it.
你是大学生 动脑筋想一下
You're a college kid. Use your head.
救救自己跟你的朋友
Save yourself and your friends.
莫斯...
Mose...
你没事吧?
you okay?
我需要来一杯
I could do with a drink.
但我不会的
I won't.
你可以相信我 安琪拉
You can count on me,Angela.
以前没有人相信我可以办好事情...
I know not too many people have counted on me in the past to do anything right...
今晚我要重新开始
but I'm turning over a new leaf, starting tonight.
我会带救兵回来 我保证
I will be back with help. I promise.
你何不答应他们的要求? 把那个老头交给他们
Why don't you just give them what they want? Give them the old man.
- 救兵到了后再去抓他们  - 不 我要伸张正义
- You can track them when you have help.  - No. I want justice.
伸张正义?
Justice?
我男朋友的正义又在哪里? 他的屍体就躺在门前
What about justice for my boyfriend whose body is lying on your porch?
葛斯的正义又在哪里?
What about justice for Gus,huh?
你还不懂吗?
Don't you see?
如果我放了他 你永远无法为你男朋友伸张正义
If I let him go,you may never get justice for your boyfriend.
听着 我很遗憾你遇上这种事 但你无法改变我的心意
Look,I'm sorry about what happened to you,but you're not changing my mind.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
我们上吧
Let's do this.
我车上有无线电 随时保持联络 小心点
There's a radio in my truck. Keep in constant contact and be careful.
我的车停在回收场旁边的加油站
My truck is at the gas station by the junkyard.
我会掩护你
I'll cover you.
快去
Go. Go,go.
(警长)
天啊 快点 拜托快发动
God,come on,come on,come on. Please,please,please start.
你可以的
You can do it.
莫斯 你听到了吗?
Mose,can you hear me?
我听到了 警长 我正要飞奔赶过去
I got you,sheriff. I'm on my way like a bat out of hell.
我要你安全抵达
I need you there in one piece.
别开太快 好吗?
Not too fast,okay?
收到
Roger that.
(速限55英里)
我刚上公路 警长
I'm just getting on the highway now,sheriff.
没看到他们
No sign of them.
很好 保持联络
Good,keep me posted.
我说过我不会让你...
I told you,I wouldn't let you...
该死
Shit.
莫斯?
Mose?
莫斯? 请回答
Mose? Come in,Mose.
莫斯?
Mose?
比利跟朱利安早该回来了 对吧?
Billy and Julian should have been back by now,shouldn't they?
我知道
I know.
他们死了 对吧?
They're dead,aren't they?
我们并不知道
We don't know that.
我不要死在这里
I don't wanna die here.
我也是
Neither do I.
我要离开
I wanna leave.
我们无处可去
There's no place to go.
这里一定有车
There must be a car or a truck or something.
- 莫斯开走我唯一的车  - 我可以偷辆车 什么都可以
- Mose took my only truck. - Well, then I'll steal a car. Anything.
我得离开这里
I just need to get the fuck out of here.
你会接电线启动引擎吗?
You know how to hot-wire a car?
我不会
No.
听着 音乐节就要结束 我的手下都会回来
Look,the festival will be over soon. My deputies will be back.
我们只要再等一下
We just have to wait a little longer.
- 如果我等不了那么久呢?  - 你没有选择
- And what if I can't wait that long?  - You really don't have a choice.
一个人跑到外面简直是自杀行为
To go out there now by yourself would be suicide.
除非你跟我一起走
Not if you come with me.
我不能离开这里
I can't leave here.
现在只剩下我们两个
There's two of us left.
如果他们真的来救他 我们该怎么办?
What can we possibly do if they come for him?
我们得尽力而为
Our best.
我想你比他更疯狂
I think you're crazier than he is.
警长 救救我
Sheriff. Help me,sheriff.
警长!
Sheriff!
警长 救救我
Sheriff. Sheriff. Help me.
不 拜托 别这样
Oh,no. Please. Don't do it.
救救我
Help me.
你可以突袭她
You can surprise her.
抢走她的武器 逼她放了我
Take her weapon and force her to let me out.
- 我办不到  - 她只是一个女人
- I can't.  - She's just a woman.
别烦我
Leave me alone.
我要你活下来
I wanna see you live.
你很聪明 丽塔 你太聪明了 不该死掉
You're smart,Lita. Too smart to die.
我要你别烦我
I said,leave me alone.
你比你的朋友都聪明
You're smarter than your friends.
该死 你曾逃出我孩子的魔掌
Hell,you even got away from my boys once.
你有资格活下来
You deserve to live.
我会要我的孩子们放你一马...
I will tell my boys to let you live...
如果你愿意帮我
if you help me.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
好吧...
Well...
如果你站在那里 什么都不做 你跟那个臭女人死定了
you and that bitch are certainly gonna die if you just stand there and do nothing.
我可以跟你保证那一点
That I can guarantee you.
不
No.
不!
No!
不
No.
你听到了吗?
Do you hear that?
什么?
What?
是莫斯
It's Mose.
那个声音是从哪来传来的?
Well,where's it coming from?
(易燃气体)
他在二手商店里 来吧 拿着这个
He's in the thrift store. Here,take this.
看着他 有人敢闯进来 格杀勿论
Watch him. If anyone comes in,shoot them.
- 什么...? 你打算怎么办?  - 我只能尽力而为
- Wha... What are you gonna do?  - What I can.
天啊
Oh,God.
你的机会来了
Now's your chance.
不
No.
别傻了
Oh,don't be stupid.
救救自己
Save yourself.
把眼光放远
Have some vision.
你很聪明
You're smart.
你想活下去 对吧?
And you wanna live,don't you?
没错
Yes.
那就把门打开
Well,then open this cell.
我会离开 我的孩子们也一样
I will go away and so will my boys.
考虑一下
Think.
- 我怎么能相信你呢?  - 你有枪 对吧?
- How can I trust you?  - Well,you have the gun,don't you?
打开门...
You open this cell...
我会离开
and I will walk away.
我保证
Promise.
钥匙在左边的枪柜上
The keys are in the gun locker to your left.
就是那样
That's it.
乖女孩
Good girl.
只要把锁打开就行了
It is as simple as turning a key in a lock.
你手上握着的钥匙能救你一命
That right there in your hand is the key to your life.
如果我放了你...
If I let you out of here...
你会放了我 对吧?
you let me go free,right?
你跟你的人不会追杀我
You and your men, you don't come after me.
那是我的条件 好吗?
That's the deal,right?
就这么说定
Done deal.
如果你敢搞鬼...
If you try anything...
我对天发誓 我会杀了你
I swear to God,I will kill you.
我只想离开这里
All I want is to get out of here.
退后
Back up.
快点
Go.
好吧 慢慢出来
Okay,get out of here. Slowly.
来吧
Move.
丽塔 你做了正确决定
You know,Lita,you did the right thing.
快离开这里
Just get out of here.
对了...
Oh,and,uh...
还记得我说过要把眼光放远吗?
you know what I was saying about vision?
快来人救救我
Somebody help me.
- 丽塔  - 我的眼睛
- Lita?  - My eyes.
天啊
God.
我警告过你 臭女人
I warned you,bitch.
该死
Goddamn it.
丽塔 来吧
Lita. Come on. Come on.
- 我的眼睛  - 你会没事的
- My eyes.  - You're gonna be all right.
- 你会没事的  - 我的眼睛
- You're gonna be all right.  - My eyes.
来吧
Come on.
- 来吧 快点  - 天啊
- Come on. Go.  - Oh,my God.
天啊
Oh,my God.
把手举高
Get your fucking hands up.
- 快点...  - 去死吧!
- Get...  - Fuck you. Ow!
我会帮你包扎止血 好吗?
I'm gonna bandage you to stop the bleeding,okay?
头往后仰
Put your head back.
天啊 我太蠢了
Oh,God,I'm so stupid.
好了 甜心
Okay,sweetie,okay.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
他答应过的
He promised.
他答应如果我放了他 他会离开
He promised he would just leave if I let him out.
- 你相信他?  - 我不知道还能怎么办
- And you believed him?  - I didn't know what else to do.
丽塔 如果我们想活着看到天亮 你得听我的话
Lita,you're gonna have to listen to me if we're gonna make it out alive.
- 你能那么做吗?  - 好的
- Can you do that?  - Yes.
很好
Good.
我呢? 我在流血
What about me? I'm bleeding here.
对 你得靠自己
Yeah,you're on your own.
我很乐意看着你死去
Oh,I'm gonna enjoy watching you die.
你会比我先死
Not if you die first.
来吧 再对我开枪
Go ahead. Shoot me again.
- 把事情做个了断  - 别挑衅我
- Get it over with.  - Don't tempt me.
你这个胆小鬼
You're a fucking coward.
你根本就没胆
You don't have the guts.
我会到场看着他们处死你
I'm gonna be there when they stick a needle in your arm.
对
Yeah.
你只是在说大话安慰自己
Well,you just go right on telling yourself that,baby.
我去求援
I'm gonna go for help.
你待在这里 什么都别做
You stay here and don't do anything, okay?
- 我出去后会把门锁上  - 你再也回不来了 臭女人
- I'm gonna lock the door behind me.  - You ain't never coming back,bitch.
傑森?
Jason?
傑森
Jason.
不 傑森
No. Oh,no. Jason.
天啊 不
Oh,my God. Oh,my God. No.
天啊
Oh,God.
我要你记得这个声音 丽塔...
I want you to remember this voice,Lita...
因为这会是你最后听到的声音
because it's gonna be the last one you'll ever hear.
我会在你的耳边低语 然后割断你的喉咙...
I'm gonna whisper in your ear right before I slit your throat...
那只是迟早的问题
which is only a matter of time now.
闭嘴
Just shut up. Shut up.
或许我不会立刻杀了你
Maybe I won't kill you right away.
或许我会让你多活几分钟
Maybe I'll keep you alive a little while.
对
Yeah.
因为我要强暴你
Because I'm gonna fuck you.
不
No. Ha-ha-ha.
闭嘴!
Shut up,just shut up!
然后我的三个孩子会强暴你
And then my three boys are gonna fuck you.
不
No.
我们完事后...
And then when we're done...
我会把你的乳头割下来当纪念品
I'm gonna cut your titties off as a souvenir.
天啊
Oh,God.
你可以逃
You run away.
那样会更好玩
That makes it more fun.
逃吧 小女孩
You run,little girl.
因为我要来抓你了
Because I'm coming to get you.
看起来我们团圆了 警长?
Well,now,looks like we've come full circle,huh,sheriff?
我最爱讽刺别人了
I love irony.
- 你呢?  - 他们会抓到你的
- Don't you?  - They'll find you.
我很怀疑
On,I highly doubt that.
我们准备离开镇上
We're just fixing to leave town.
我希望你在地狱里被烈火灼身
I hope you burn in hell.
抱歉让你失望了 会被烈火灼身的人是你
Well,now,sorry to disappoint, but you're the one that's gonna burn.
好了 孩子们 那样就可以了
All right,boys,that will do it.
警长 我是个好心人...
Now,sheriff, out of the kindness of my heart...
我要给你选择机会...
I am offering you a choice...
因为我是个绅士 你觉得呢?
which is real gentleman-like of me, don't you think?
去你的
Fuck you.
嘿
Oh. Heh,heh.
你要拼到最后一刻吗?
A fighter to the end,huh?
我很佩服
Admirable.
好了...
Now...
我是个好心人 我跟你解释一下我要怎么做
as I am a man of mercy,let me explain to you what is happening here.
我会用胶带将霰弹枪黏在你嘴巴上...
I am gonna duct tape this shotgun to your mouth...
将电线绑在板机上...
and I have attached a wire to the trigger...
另一端绑在你脚上
which is also attached to your foot.
只要你将脚跟放下...
So that when you come down off your tippy-toes...
电线会拉动板机
the wire is gonna pull the trigger.
基本上我是提供你一条捷径 警长
Essentially,I am offering you a way out, sheriff.
换作是我 我会答应的...
If I were you,I would take it...
因为被烧死真的很痛苦
because burning to death is one painful way to die.
你这个大混蛋
You son of a bitch.
倒数计时了 警长
Tick tock,sheriff.
我得走了
Gotta go.
好了 那样应该没问题
There,that ought to do it.
现在你只要...
Now,all you have to do...
放弃
is let go.
将脚跟放下:
Heels to the floor and:
爆炸
Boom.
就结束了
No more.
你不必谢我 警长
Oh,you don't need to thank me,sheriff.
你还撑着吗?
You hang on in there,huh?
好吧 该离开这里了
All right,let's get out of here.
停车
Stop.
停车 拜托
Stop. Please.
停车
Stop.
救救我
Help me.
拜托救救我
Please help me.
救救我
Help me.
拜托救救我
Please help me.
求求你
Oh,please.
谢天谢地 你停车了
Oh,thank God you stopped.
他们杀了我朋友
They killed my friends.
你得报警 他们要杀了警长 拜托
You need to call the police before they kill the sheriff,please.
拜托救救我
Please help me.
谢天谢地
Oh,thank God.
Thank God.
欢迎你回来 丽塔
Welcome home,Lita.
不!
No!
Ha-ha-ha! No!
不!
No!